[EP02]
Young Marshal, please spare us.
Miss Su and Master Chu
are just ordinary friends.
She has always been affectionate to you.
Affectionate?
Bring me what you dropped.
This is the precious trauma medicine
from Hongyi Hall.
Chu Nanfeng,
you care more about my wife
than I do.
You're awake.
We're investigating
the Prohibited Drug Case.
If you're innocent,
just be
a good young wife.
It smells like
trauma medicine.
My Lady.
What are you doing?
She's still sick.
Do you know
how many lives
this medicine can save on the battlefield?
Yet you used up the whole bottle.
My Lady.
The carotid artery is here.
If you want me dead,
squeeze here.
You're provoking me.
There is a red pill
at the bottom of this medicine bottle,
called Emergency Pill.
Its effect
is faster than the powder.
On the battlefield,
the powder is used for the minor,
while the red pill
is used for the serious.
Young Marshal,
She only drinks boiled water.
The water in the cup
is just poured when she drinks.
She has a hard life in the mansion.
Besides, her wound hasn't healed yet.
Please forgive her.
Young Marshal,
Miss Ye and A-Wang are asking to meet you.
Let them in.
A-Wang,
Do you remember what I told you?
Yes.
Behave yourself.
Cousin,
I brought A-Wang
to see you and your sister.
I also brought some pastries.
You can try them.
That's the bad woman.
Last time she and a man saw me and pinched me.
It hurt so much.
What?
No wonder A-Wang ran back crying.
Sister,
how could you do such a thing?
A-Wang,
come here,
be good.
Tell me,
what exactly happened?
It's this bad woman,
she was standing with a tall uncle,
and they were close together.
At this age,
in this era,
you should be learning to read.
If you lie,
your nose will grow.
Wang!
Wang, what's wrong?
Su Muwan, how dare you poison her!
I just woke up,
and Ling Shenxing gave her the pastry.
If you're jealous,
behave yourself!
Wang!
Water!
Get some water!
Don't give her water!
Don't pat her back!
What are you doing?
If anything happens to Wang,
you'll be responsible!
If you want to see her die,
just keep on blocking.
Move aside.
Miss.
Wang.
It's okay now.
Miss.
Are you okay?
Chayu.
Let them out.
It's okay.
Cousin.
[It seems that Su Muwan is in danger here.]
[Her husband doesn't love her.]
[Ye Jinrou regards her as a rival in love,]
[and targets her everywhere.]
[I have to find a way to get out of here.]
The news of Commander Ling's disappearance
has spread throughout the city.
Ling Shenxing and the others
will probably find this place soon.
This is the jade pendant
you asked us to find.
The water in this city
needs to be muddier.
Since my heart is on the right side,
I won't die.
But to go back,
I have to die again.
My lady, what are you doing?
Don't do anything stupid.
Let go.
Young Master Chu Nanfeng sent a message.
He will try to help the Su family.
Chu Nanfeng?
Who is he?
My lady,
you forgot again?
Chu Nanfeng
is your brother's good friend.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter anymore.
The most important thing now
is that I can go back.
I only read the beginning of this book.
I have no idea what's in the rest of the book.
You can't do anything stupid anymore.
You should cherish your life.
You don't understand.
That's why I have to die
that's why I have to die.
Give it to me.
No.
Come in.
Young Madam,
this is the jewelry box, fragrance powder and tonic
scented powder and tonic.
The jewelry was selected by Ye's owner.
It's the most fashionable now.
This scented powder is called Prelude to Water Melody.
There's only one box in Yang City.
Ladies in the capital city are all using it.
It's very precious.
I heard that it can be fragrant for ten years.
Don't you introduce this steamed cake?
This is made by the small kitchen.
I saw you just woke up,
so I think this kind of easily-digestible food
is suitable for you.
This cake smells strange.
Yes, it's saxitoxin.
This lethal poison is not common.
The killer is skilled in medicine.
But this has made me happy.
I can go home after I die.
Go get some water.
Go.
Don't think about it anymore.
Miss.
Help!
Somebody help!
I can finally go home.
Miss.
Why do you treat
our Miss like this?
How dare you!
Don't kill her!
Leave.
Go find a doctor!
My lady, hold on!
I'll get the doctor!
Hold on!
Don't you want me dead?
If I want someone dead,
there are countless legitimate ways.
Now,
I don't allow you to die.
Ling Shenxing,
you are so powerful.
What do you want?
You don't have to play the victim.
I don't want anything.
I just want to go home.
Su Muwan.
She's changed.
She's not as affected as before.
What happened?